// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "To create an object ______ is used.",
    answer: "constructor",
    options: [
      "class",
      "constructor",
      "User-defined functions",
      "In-built functions"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "_____ represents an entity in the real world with its identity and behaviour.    ",
    answer: "An object",
    options: [
      "An object",
      "An operator",
      "A class",
      "A method"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Private member of a class is visible to",
    answer : "Same class",
    options: [
      "Everyone",
      "Same package",
      "Same class",
      "Sub class"
      ]
      
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of following is shared structure of a set of similar objects",
    answer: "Class",
    options: [
      "Inheritance",
      "Class",
      "Abstraction",
      "Encapsulation"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which one is not true?",
    answer: "The value of a private variable in the superclass can be changed in the subclass",
    options: [
      "A non-private method in a superclass can be overridden",
      "A derived class is a subset of a superclass",
      "The value of a private variable in the superclass can be changed in the subclass",
      "When invoking the constructor from a subclass, the constructor of the superclass is automatically invoked"
    ]
  },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "In python, what is method inside class?",
     answer: "function",
     options: [
       "attribute",
       "object",
       "argument",
       "function"
     ]
   },
    {
     numb: 7,
     question: "Which of the following is correct with respect to OOP concept in Python?",
     answer: "Objects are real world entities while classes are not real.",
     options: [
       "Objects are real world entities while classes are not real.",
       "Classes are real world entities while objects are not real.",
       "Both objects and classes are real world entities.",
       "Both object and classes are not real."
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 8,
     question: "Suppose B is a subclass of A, to invoke the __init__ method in A from B, what is the line of code you should write?",
     answer: "A.__init__(self)",
     options: [
       "A.__init__(self)",
       "B.__init__(self)       ",
       "A.__init__(B)       ",
       "B.__init__(A)       "
     ]
   },
  {
     numb: 9,
     question: "What does built-in function type do in context of classes?",
     answer: "Determines the class name of any value",
     options: [
       "Determines the object name of any value       ",
       "Determines the class name of any value",
       "Determines class description of any value       ",
       "Determines the file name of any value       "
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 10,
     question: "Which of the following is not a type of inheritance?     ",
     answer: "Double-level",
     options: [
       "Double-level",
       "Multi-level",
       "Single-level",
       "Multiple"
     ]
   },
];